Guide to the Andrei Voznesenskii Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 4: Clippings
  - Subseries 4.1: About / Mentioning A.Voznesenskii
    - Subsubseries 4.1.1: Critics and Readers about A.Voznesenskii
      - Richardson, L., "A Cold War Turning Point on Tape"11.13.1999, Three identical photocopies of a clipping, 3 pages total, slightly damaged. (Box 39, Folder 43)
        Lynda Richardson; Nikita Khrushchev.; "The New York Times".
      - Stoianova, V., "Realnostta e tvorenie, nev''zmozhno v nikakva fantastika"06.09.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 39, Folder 44)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Realnostta e tvorenie, nev''zmozhno v nikakva fantastika" by Valia Stoianova from the newspaper "Novinar" (in Bulgarian).
        Valia Stoianova.; "Novinar".
      - Vaizer, T., "Voznesenskii na opernoi stsene"10.27.-11.02.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper and a photocopy of a clipping, 1 page, slightly damaged. (Box 39, Folder 45)
        An article "Voznesenskii na opernoi stsene" by Tat'iana Vaizer from the newspaper "Literaturnaia gazeta" (2 copies).
        Tat'iana Vaizer.; "Literaturnaia gazeta".
      - "Voznesenski podari kniga na Stoianov"06.09.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper and a photocopy of a clipping, 1 page, slightly damaged. (Box 39, Folder 46)
        A notice "Voznesenski podari kniga na Stoianov" from the newspaper "Monitor" (2 copies, in Bulgarian).
        Petr [?] Stoianov.; "Monitor".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Beloe zoloto", "Sladostrastie", "Delib - debilam", "Rybki"10.16.1999, Two fragments of an issue of a newspaper (one with two additions / corrections), damaged. (Box 39, Folder 47)
        A collection of poems (incl. "Beloe zoloto", "Sladostrastie", "Delib - debilam", and "Rybki") by A.Voznesenskii and a notice from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets" (2 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Beregite zaik!"05.05.1999, An issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 39, Folder 48)
        A collection of poems "Beregite zaik!" by A.Voznesenskii with a small notice from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Devochka s pirsingom"07.07.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper and a photocopy of a clipping, 1 A3 page with several handwritten notes on the other side, damaged. (Box 39, Folder 49)
        A poem "Devochka s pirsingom" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets" (2 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Gernika Sapgira"10.14.1999, A photocopy of a clipping, 1 page, damaged. (Box 39, Folder 50)
        An essay "Gernika Sapgira" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Obshchaia gazeta" [?].
        Genrikh Sapgir.; "Obshchaia gazeta" [?].
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Strakh"09.22.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 39, Folder 51)
        A poem "Strakh" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Komsomol'skaia pravda".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Vecher 19 oktiabria"10.18.1999, Two fragments of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 1)
        A collection of poems "Vecher 19 oktiabria" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets" (2 copies).
      - "Voznesenskii v Novoi opere"10.16-22.1999, A photocopy of a clipping, 1 page, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 2)
        A notice "Voznesenskii v Novoi opere" by A.Voznesenskii from a newspaper.
      - Voznesenskii, A., Baranov, A., About the meeting with N.Khrushchev12.07.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 3)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Andreiu Voznesenskomu pokazalos', chto Nikita Sergeevich byl p'ian" by Andrei Baranov and an article "Glaza u Khrushcheva zakatilis', on oral: 'Pasport vam v zuby!' " from the newspaper "Komsomol'skaia pravda".
        Nikita Khrushchev; Andrei Baranov.; "Komsomol'skaia pravda".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Bogachinskaia, I., "Tak chto zhe est' istina?!"; Voznesenskii, A., "Novye stikhi"11.12-14.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 4)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Tak chto zhe est' istina?!" by Inna Bogachinskaia and a collection of poems "Novye stikhi" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Vechernii New York" ["Vecherniy New York"].
        Inna Bogachinskaia.; "Vechernii New York" ["Vecherniy New York"].
      - Voznesenskii, A., Chebotarev, V., "Magiia slova"[n.d.] 1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper with a handwritten note, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 5)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Magiia slova" by Vladislav Chebotarev from the newspaper "Mir zazerkal'ia".
        Vladislav Chebotarev.; "Mir zazerkal'ia".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Kalinina-Artemova, A., Voitsekhovskii, B., Kuz'mina, V., "Pushkin prokuratoru podsunul shmaru, Pushkin akkuratno podzheg Samaru"04.20.1999, An issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 6)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Pushkin prokuratoru podsunul shmaru, Pushkin akkuratno podzheg Samaru" by Anna Kalinina-Artemova, Boris Voitsekhovskii, and Viktoriia Kuz'mina from the newspaper "Komsomol'skaia pravda".
        Anna Kalinina-Artemova; Boris Voitsekhovskii; Viktoriia Kuz'mina.; "Komsomol'skaia pravda".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Leikina, I., "Vek genial'nykh prestupnikov i genial'nykh poetov"; Voznesenskii, A., "Vot i sgorel vrode sputnikov...", "Pereulok", "Doneslos' po sviazi sotovoi...", "Russkaia erotika", "Vdol' moria", "A ty menia pomnish'?"11.13-14.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 7)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Vek genial'nykh prestupnikov i genial'nykh poetov" by Irina Leikina and a collection of poems by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Novoe russkoe slovo" ["Novoye russkoye slovo"].
        Irina Leikina.; "Novoe russkoe slovo" ["Novoye russkoye slovo"].
      - Voznesenskii, A., Pipin, V., "Poet v Rossii - ne bol'she, chem poet"07.02.1999, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 8)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Poet v Rossii - ne bol'she, chem poet" by Vitalii Pinini from the newspaper "Segodnia".
        Vitalii Pinin.; "Segodnia".
      - Zimianina, N., "Nu chto nam nado eshche ot nego?"10.23.1999, A photocopy of a clipping with a handwritten note, 1 page. (Box 40, Folder 9)
        An article "Nu chto nam nado eshche ot nego?" by Natalia Zimianina from a newspaper.
        Natalia Zimianina.
      - Boguslavskaia, Z., Saed-Shakh, A., "Mozhete nazvat' eto bogemoi"08.03.2000, Three photocopies of a clipping with several handwritten marks, 3 pages total, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 10)
        An interview with Zoia Boguslavskaia "Mozhete nazvat' eto bogemoi" by Anna Saed-Shakh from the newspaper "Vecherniaia Moskva" (3 copies).
        Zoia Boguslavskaia; Anna Saed-Shakh.; "Vecherniaia Moskva".
      - Dinwiddie, K., "Russian writers to visit campus"04.10.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper with a handwritten mark, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 11)
        A notice "Russian writers to visit campus" by Keith Dinwiddie from the newspaper "The Oklahoma Daily".
        Zoia Boguslavskaia; Keith Dinwiddie.; "The Oklahoma Daily".
      - Galina, M., "Voznesenskii osvaivaet novoe tysiacheletie"12.6-12.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper and a photocopy of a clipping, 1 page, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 12)
        An notice "Voznesenskii osvaivaet novoe tysiacheletie" by M.Galina from the newspaper "Literaturnaia gazeta" (2 copies).
        M.Galina.; "Literaturnaia gazeta".
      - Gubailovskii, V., "Andrei Voznesenskii v Internete"12.06.2000, Two photocopies of a clipping, 2 pages total, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 13)
        An article "Andrei Voznesenskii v Internete" by Vladimir Gubailovskii from the newspaper "Nezavisimaia gazeta" [?] (2 copies).
        Vladimir Gubailovskii.; "Nezavisimaia gazeta" [?].
      - Katsiuba, E., "Voznesenskii - Telets..."[n.d.] 2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 14)
        An article "Voznesenskii - Telets..." by Elena Katsiuba from the newspaper "Goroskop" (the end is missing).
        Elena Katsiuba.; "Goroskop".
      - Kedrov, K., "Dekabr' v Peredelkino"12.06.2000, A photocopy of a clipping with a handwritten mark, 1 page. (Box 40, Folder 15)
        An article "Dekabr' v Peredelkino" by Konstantin Kedrov from the newspaper "Novye Izvestiia".
      - Khlebnikov, O., "Tysiacheletie, tret'im budesh'?"; Voznesenskii, A., Poetry12.25-31.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 16)
        An article "Tysiacheletie, tret'im budesh'?" by Oleg Khlebnikov and a collection of poems by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Novaia gazeta".
      - "Komsomol'skaia pravda"12.23.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper with several handwritten notes, severely damaged. (Box 40, Folder 17)
        A fragment of an issue of the newspaper "Komsomol'skaia pravda" with several handwritten notes made by A.Voznesenskii [?].
      - "Kulisa NG"03.17.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 18)
        A fragment of an issue of the newspaper "Kulisa NG".
        "Kulisa NG".
      - Marchenko, A., "Sem' s polovinoi, ili Proshchanie s arkhivekom"01.26-02.01.2000, A photocopy of a clipping, 4 pages total, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 19)
        An article "Sem' s polovinoi, ili Proshchanie s arkhivekom" by Alla Marchenko from the newspaper "Literaturnaia gazeta".
        Alla Marchenko.; "Literaturnaia gazeta".
      - Novikov, L., "Mozaika Voznesenskogo"08.16.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 20)
        An article "Mozaika Voznesenskogo" by Leonid Novikov from the newspaper "Izvestiia".
        Leonid Novikov.; "Izvestiia".
      - Tsvetkov, Iu., "Ne poseshchaite khudozhnika posle konchiny, a naveshchaite, poka vy zhivy"12.05.2000, Two photocopies of a clipping, 2 pages total, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 21)
        A notice "Ne poseshchaite khudozhnika posle konchiny, a naveshchaite, poka vy zhivy" by Iurii Tsvetkov from the newspaper "Komsomol'skaia pravda - Moskva" [?].
        Iurii Tsvetkov.; "Komsomol'skaia pravda - Moskva" [?].
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Chat molchan'ia"11.01[?].2000, A photocopy of a proof [?], 1 A3 page, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 22)
        A poem "Chat molchan'ia" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Komsomol'skaia pravda".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Chat molchan'ia"11.25.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper. (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Chitaite, zaviduite: ia - grazhdanin soedinennykh chatov"11.11.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 24)
        Fragments of the poem "Chat" by A.Voznesenskii with a short editorial notice from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Pen-novosti"05.24.2000, Two fragments of an issue of a newspaper and a photocopy of a clipping, 2 pages, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 25)
        A collection of poems and a short notice by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets" (3 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Perekhod na Pushkinskoi"08.11.2000, A photocopy of a clipping with a short handwritten note, 1 page, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 26)
        A poem "Perekhod na Pushkinskoi" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Samokaty", "Miloserdiia!", "Utrennik"11.29.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 27)
        Three poems by A.Voznesenskii and a short editorial notice from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Teriaiu golos"03.17.2000, Three fragments of a proof [?], 1 A4 and 2 A3 pages, annotated, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 28)
        A collection of poems by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Kulisa-NG" (3 incomplete copies).
        "Kulisa-NG".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Teriaiu golos" / "Vozvrashchenie golosa"03.03.2000, A proof [?] and five fragments of a proof [?], 2 A4 and 5 A3 pages total, annotated, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 29)
        A collection of poems by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Kulisa-NG" (6 copies, five of them incomplete).
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Vifleem" & "Millenium"01.11.2000, A proof [?] and four photocopies of a proof [?], 5 pages of different size total, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 30)
        Two poems by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Nezavisimaia gazeta" (3 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Vremia poshlo!"05.24-30.2000, Three fragments of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 31)
        A collection of poems and an essay "Uliss ulits" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Literaturnaia gazeta" (3 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., Bondarenko, S., "Poslednii Stradivari sostradan'ia"08.14.2000, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, severely damaged. (Box 40, Folder 32)
        An article "Poslednii Stradivari sostradan'ias" by Stanislav Bondarenko from the newspaper "Kievskie vedomosti".
        Stanislav Bondarenko.; "Kievskie vedomosti".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Chebotarev, V., "Magiia slova Andreia Voznesenskogo"[n.d.] 2000, An issue of a almanach with a handwritten dedication, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 33)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Magiia slova Andreia Voznesenskogo" by Vladislav Chebotarev from the almanach "Vse muzy Rossii" with a handwritten dedication from Vladislav Chebotarev to Andrei Voznesenskii on the back of the front cover.
        Vladislav Chebotarev.; "Vse muzy Rossii".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Galanter, V., "Intimnyi al'bom"04.11.2000, An issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 34)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Intimnyi al'bom" by Viktor Galanter from the newspaper "Vecherniaia Moskva".
        Viktor Galanter.; "Vecherniaia Moskva".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Makarov, D., "Poet, vlast' i Internet"12.05.2000, Two photocopies of a clipping, 2 pages total, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 35)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Poet, vlast' i Internet" by Dmitrii Makarov from the newspaper "Argumenty i fakty" (2 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., Ovchinnikova, S., "Dvoinoe otkrytie Andreia Voznesenskogo"[n.d.] 2000 [?], A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 36)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Dvoinoe otkrytie Andreia Voznesenskogo" by Svetlana Ovchinnikova from the newspaper "Orakul".
        Svetlana Ovchinnikova.; "Orakul".
      - "Andrei Voznesenskii - poet mirovoi"[n.d.] 2001, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 37)
        A short interview with A.Voznesenskii and a poem "Bard v pogonakh" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Argumenty i fakty - Moskva".
        Oleg Rubezhov.; "Argumenty i fakty - Moskva".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Beremennyi bas"02.28.2001, Two fragments of an issue of a newspaper and a photocopy of a clipping, 4 pages, annotated, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 38)
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Chasy sycha"04.21-22.2001, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 39)
        A short interview with A.Voznesenskii by Irina Leikina and a collection of poems "Chasy sycha" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Novoe russkoe slovo" ["Novoye russkoye slovo"].
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Gde vykhod?", "Trade Center", "XXL"09.17.2001, Two fragments of an issue of a newspaper and a fax copy [?] of a proof [?], 3 pages (incomplete), with numerous handwritten notes on the other side, annotated, damaged. (Box 40, Folder 40)
        A collection of poems by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets" (3 copies, one is incomplete).
        Zoia Boguslavskaia.; "Moskovskii komsomolets".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Ia - sal'to perevernutoi Otchizny..."; Voznesenskii, A., Rostovtseva, I., "Magicheskie ochki"January - February 2001, An issue of a magazine with several handwritten corrections / additions. (Box 40, Folder 41)
        A collection of poems and "videomas" "Ia - sal'to perevernutoi Otchizny..." by A.Voznesenskii and an interview with A.Voznesenskii "Magicheskie ochki" by Inna Rostovtseva from the magazine "VIP".
        Inna Rostovtseva.; "VIP".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "My stali ekonomikadze (Iz novykh stikhov)"April 2001, An issue of a magazine, slightly damaged. (Box 40, Folder 42)
        A collection of poems and "videomas" "My stali ekonomikadze (Iz novykh stikhov)" by A.Voznesenskii from the magazine "Rossiiskaia Federatsiia segodnia".
        Inna Rostovtseva.; "Rossiiskaia Federatsiia segodnia".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Ne vse my - sobaki"08.03.2001, Two fragments of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 1)
        A poem "Sharpei" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets" (2 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Novye stikhi"01.10.2001, An issue of a newspaper, an annotated fragment of a newspaper, and an annotated photocopy of a clipping, 1 page, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 2)
        A collection of poems "Novye stikhi" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets" (3 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Novye stikhi"12.30.2001, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 3)
        A collection of poems "Novye stikhi" and a short essay by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Shar ada"12.12-18.2001, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 4)
        A collection of poems "Shar ada" and a short essay by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Literaturnaia gazeta".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Sharpei"08.03.2001, A photocopy of a clipping (a proof ?), 4 pages, slightly damaged. (Box 41, Folder 5)
        A poem "Sharpei" by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Stakan vodki - veshch' mirovogo klassa"05.18.2001, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 6)
        A short notice by A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Komsomol'skaia pravda - Moskva".
        "Komsomol'skaia pravda - Moskva".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Bondarenko, S., "Kak Andrei Voznesenskii meshal ideinym pisateliam stroit' sotsializm"11.03.2001, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 7)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Kak Andrei Voznesenskii meshal ideinym pisateliam stroit' sotsializm" by Stanislav Bondarenko from the newspaper "Kievskie vedomosti" (the end is missing).
      - Voznesenskii, A., Karpovich, I., "U nas tri vraga - totalitarizm, totalizator i total'noe lizanie"08.27.2001, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 8)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "U nas tri vraga - totalitarizm, totalizator i total'noe lizanie" by Inna Karpovich from the newspaper "Vesti segodnia".
        Inna Karpovich.; "Vesti segodnia".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Nuzov, V., [An interview]04.19-25.2001, Two fragments of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 9)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii by Vladimir Nuzov from the newspaper "Russkii bazar" / "Russian Bazaar" (the beginning is missing).
        Vladimir Nuzov.; "Russkii bazar" / "Russian Bazaar" .
      - Voznesenskii, A., Solomonova, O., "Skvoz' eto imia prostupaiut ternii"02.10.2001, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper and two photocopies of a clipping, 6 pages total, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 10)
        An interview with A.Voznesenskii "Skvoz' eto imia prostupaiut ternii" by Ol'ga Solomonova from the newspaper "Trud" (3 copies).
        Ol'ga Solomonova.; "Trud" .
      - About A.Voznesenskii's plans10.17.2002, A photocopy of a clipping with several handwritten notes, 1 page, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 11)
        A short notice about A.Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Vechernii klub" [?].
        Zoia Boguslavskaia.; "Vechernii klub" [?].
      - Elin, A., "20.02.2002"02.26.2002, Two photocopies of a clipping with several handwritten notes, 2 pages total, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 12)
        An article "20.02.2002" by Anton Elin from the newspaper "Izvestiia".
        Anton Elin.; "Izvestiia".
      - Kedrov, K., "Okhrannaia gramota russkoi poezii"02.12.2002, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 41, Folder 13)
        An article "Okhrannaia gramota russkoi poezii" by Konstantin Kedrov from the newspaper "Novye Izvestiia".
      - Khokhlov, V., "Pamflet po povodu soiuzov"; S.Top, "Poet Stop nabiraet oboroty..."01.12.2002, An issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 14)
        A poem "Pamflet po povodu soiuzov" by Vladimir Khokhlov and a notice "Poet Stop nabiraet oboroty..." by S.Top from the newspaper "Budushchee Rossii".
        "Budushchee Rossii".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Mostik"October 2002, An issue of a magazine. (Box 41, Folder 15)
        A short novel "Mostik" by Andrei Voznesenskii from the magazine "Ogonek" ["Ogonyok"].
      - Voznesenskii, A., "O, Gospodi..."11.15.2002, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper and four photocopies of proofs [?], one of them annotated, 4 A3 leaves total, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 16)
        A collection of works "O, Gospodi..." by Andrei Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets".
      - Voznesenskii, A., "Zerkal'nyi god"01.03.2002, Two fragments of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 41, Folder 17)
        A collection of poems "Zerkal'nyi god" by Andrei Voznesenskii from the newspaper "Moskovskii komsomolets" (2 copies).
      - Voznesenskii, A., Kostanian, L., "Raby ne my"10.16.2002, A photocopy of a clipping with several handwritten notes, 1 A3 page, slightly damaged. (Box 41, Folder 18)
        An essay "Raby ne my" by Andrei Voznesenskii with a notice by Lev Kostanian from the newspaper "Rossiiskie vesti".
        Lev Kostanian.; "Rossiiskie vesti".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Kvaskova, E., "Chuzhoi ia zhizn'iu ne rasplachivalsia"05.27-29.2002, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, damaged. (Box 41, Folder 19)
        An article / interview with Andrei Voznesenskii "Chuzhoi ia zhizn'iu ne rasplachivalsia" by Elena Kvaskova from the newspaper "Novaia gazeta".
        Elena Kvaskova.; "Novaia gazeta".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Osipova, N., "Peredelkinskie"August 2002, An issue of a magazine. (Box 41, Folder 20)
        An interview with Andrei Voznesenskii "Peredelkinskie" by Nataliia Osipova from the magazine "Voiazh".
        Nataliia Osipova.; "Voiazh".
      - Voznesenskii, A., Vandenko, A., "Menia kormit million alykh roz..."10.08.2002, An issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 41, Folder 21)
        An interview with Andrei Voznesenskii "Menia kormit million alykh roz..." by Andrei Vandenko from the newspaper "Komsomol'skaia pravda".
        Andrei Vandenko.; "Komsomol'skaia pravda".
      - Zatevakhina, M., "Pushkin pribyl na loshadke"05.31.2002, A fragment of an issue of a newspaper, slightly damaged. (Box 41, Folder 22)
        An article "Pushkin pribyl na loshadke" by Muza Zatevakhina from the newspaper "Nezavisimaia gazeta".
        Muza Zatevakhina.; "Nezavisimaia gazeta".
      - "Conference set on Doctor Zhivago writer"04.28.2004, An issue of a newspaper. (Box 41, Folder 23)
        An article "Conference set on Doctor Zhivago writer" from the newspaper "Stanford report".
        Evgenii [Evgeny] Pasternak; Elena Pasternak; Bliss Carnochan; Vyacheslav [Viacheslav] Ivanov; Michel Aucouturier; Vittorio Strada; Olga Andreyev [Andreiev] Carlisle; Lazar Fleishman.; "Stanford report".
      - "Libraries acquire extensive collection of poet and writer Andrei Voznesensky"11.17.2004, An issue of a newspaper. (Box 41, Folder 24)
        An article "Libraries acquire extensive collection of poet and writer Andrei Voznesensky" from the newspaper "Stanford report".